<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Beyond Words</string>
    <string name="start_bt">Start</string>
    <string name="admin_bt">Admin Login</string>
    <string name="phase2_Next">Next</string>
    <string name="Submit_button">Submit</string>

    <string name="phase1InfoString">In this section, select/write all the necessary information that applies to you.
        \n\nIf any of the questions deems irrelevant to you, please provide a feedback from the options available at the bottom of the screen!
        \n\nSwipe right to get started!</string>

    <string name="phase2InfoString">In this section, describe the situation you faced.
        \n\nPlease try to limit yourself to 5 sentences and describe the entire situation in the clearest possible terms.
        \n\nShould you need any assistance, please follow the prompts on each of the text area to help you describe better.
        \n\nSwipe right and tell us!</string>

    <string name="phase3InfoString">In this section, highlight the concern you have with the described situation.
        \n\nPlease try to limit yourself to 5 sentences and bring out the major concern you have with the inter-cultural interaction.
        \n\nShould you need any assistance, please follow the prompt on the text area and start describing the concern.
        \n\nSwipe right, we\'re listening!</string>

    <string name="terms_cond">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="describe_sit">Describe your Situation</string>
    <string name="phase2_ques">In the most neutral terms, describe the situation you faced. It is recommended that you include the W"s (Who, When, What) and How in your description. Try to limit the description to 5 sentences.</string>
    <string name="terms_statement">Beyond Words is an interactive survey application designed to collect data from the user"s regarding various intercultural situations. The application aims to use the data to come up with solutions to avoid intercultural situations between people of different nationalities, cultures, or languages. \n \nThe application is free to download and use. Please note that the application does not store the user's personal information and does not share it with any third party. Beyond Words will use only the user\'s input on the intercultural situations only for analysis purposes. \n \nBy accessing the application, you accept the above-mentioned terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_concern">Identify a Concern</string>
    <string name="phase3_statement"> What are your concerns about this interaction? What questions does it raise? Or What you have learned from this situation</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
</resources>
